openskycc.com 2014-09-10

# Privacy Statement | CapitalBank

**F A C T S**

| 

**WHAT DOES CAPITAL BANK DOES WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
**Why?**

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
**What?**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have from us.  This can include:

· Social Security Number and income,

· Account balances and payment history,

· Credit history and credit scores

When you are  _no longer_  our customer, we continue to share your information  as described in this notice.  
  
**How?**

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Capital Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
**Reasons we can share your personal information**

| 

**Does Capital Bank share?**

| 

**Can you limit this sharing?**  
  
**For our everyday business purposes _  –_**

Such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our marketing purposes _  –_**

To offer our products and services to you

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

No

| 

We don’t share  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes**  – Information about your transactions and experiences

| 

No

| 

We don’t share  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes**  – Information about your creditworthiness

| 

No

| 

We don’t share  
  
**For non-affiliates to market to you  ** \- To offer their products or sevices to BSC® Secured Visa® Credit Card account holders only.  Information related to creditworthiness is not shared.

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**To limit our sharing**  on BSC® Secured Visa® Credit Card accounts

| 

· Call: 844-660-2273 between the hours of    8:30AM and 5:00PM Eastern Time (Monday through Friday)  **or**

· Mail the **  form **(click  **here **to download)

Please note:

If you are a  _new_  customer, we can begin sharing your information (30) days from the date we sent this notice. When you are  _no longer_  our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.   
  
**Questions?**

| 

Call us at 301-468-8848 or toll free at 1-877-568-4262.  Or go to [www.capitalbankmd.com](http://www.capitalbankmd.com/).  
  
  |    |    |
